ظآزThe clouds hide the faint light
behind themظآز
ظآزA lonely bench on the street cornerظآز
ظآزWhere all feelings come to restظآز
ظآزIn the night sky, the moon's trailظآز
ظآزStitches up and soothes my sorrowظآز
ظآزThe courage to get close to youظآز
ظآزDrives away my hesitationظآز
ظآزFate turns and brings us togetherظآز
ظآزI search my memories with all my mightظآز
ظآزLove catches me off guardظآز
ظآزYou, in the albumظآز
ظآزShine through my past like starlightظآز
I'll go dry my hair.
Okay.
Maybe...
ظآزMelting all my fears awayظآز
I can help you.
ظآزI'm lost in themظآز
ظآزThe world suddenly has meaningظآز
ظآزThrough the pouring rain, I found youظآز
ظآزIn the space of our embraceظآز
ظآزStars spill across the skyظآز
ظآزIn the night sky, the moon's trailظآز
ظآزStitches up and soothes my sorrowظآز
ظآزThe courage to get close to youظآز
ظآزDrives away my hesitationظآز
ظآزFate turns and brings us togetherظآز
ظآزI search my memories with all my mightظآز
ظآزLove catches me off guardظآز
ظآزYou, in the albumظآز
ظآزShine through my past like starlightظآز
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 18=
(Sharing a Bed Is Not Enough)
I...
I like...
I... I'm used to sleeping on the left.
Alright. I'll sleep on the right.
Good night.
ظآزTonight the rain falls soft and slowظآز
ظآزBlending with letters left unread
drifting through the airظآز
ظآزYou turn and look back at meظآز
ظآزIn those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appearظآز
ظآزIt feels like we have carried so muchظآز
ظآزSo many questions time itself
could not make clearظآز
ظآزThe moment you walked into my lifeظآز
ظآزEvery dream I had became something
I want with you nearظآز
We've cut off Minghui's core suppliers.
Any reaction from Shen Gu?
Nothing so far.
He's just picking Xu Wanxin up
and dropping her off at work
like a live-in husband.
Their raw material supply
has been cut off now.
They'll last three months top.
Given Minghui's strength,
they'll find new suppliers
sooner or later.
Keep the pressure on Minghui,
or stop now...
If we stop now,
everything we've done goes to waste.
If Shen Gu won't move,
hit his weak spot.
After all, Xu Wanxin
is his wife in name.
Use Raymond Group's
platform and media system.
I want Xu Wanxin to wake up tomorrow
and find her reputation ruined.
Grandfather.
Did you sleep well last night?
Grandfather,
I'm heading to work.
Can't bear to leave me?
Hurry along.
The company needs you.
Okay.
Grandfather,
we'll come back often.
Alright.
I'll get going too.
Morning, Ms. Wanxin.
Morning.
Ms. Wanxin, Ms. Xu's here.
She's waiting in the meeting room.
Xi?
Yes.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Okay. Got it. You may go.
Ms. Wanxin, good morning.
Morning.
Ms. Wanxin.
Xi.
What's wrong? Missed me?
What has happened?
What's with that face?
Gossip from last night.
It spreads insanely fast.
Today,
we're breaking down Gang City's
biggest scandal among the rich families,
(Shocking Financial Expos├ر)
the breakup of the Shen and Xu families.
Fill me in.
I'm totally lost.
Marriages between the rich
are capital reshuffling games.
Sorry to interrupt.
Look at this.
Xu Wanxin's father just passed away,
and right after that, she dumped Shen Hao,
the heir of Junlin Group,
and married his rival, Shen Gu,
who is currently
the largest shareholder of Junlin Group.
Their relationship is complicated.
What's crazier is
that she changed her husband
in just three days.
Right after that,
she announced cooperation
with Qingniao Group.
What kind of relationship is that
for Qingniao Group
to support Minghui Group?
Celebrities always
want to marry into wealth.
Miss Xu wants to climb higher too.
Of course she'd find a stronger backer.
That's disgusting.
I'm taking them to court.
They're not just trying to destroy
your marriage with Wanxin,
but they also want to shake
Minghui's credibility.
Look at the spread.
Twelve major platforms
are pushing it at once.
Over 100 million views in 24 hours.
Shen Tingyuan really
went all in this time.
Are they insane?
Boss, the trace is back.
The source is media
under the Raymond Group.
No wonder they bypassed
our monitoring system.
Raymond missed out on you before,
and now we've taken their market.
They have certainly been trying
to suppress us.
Yes.
We've confirmed cooperation
between Raymond Group and Shen Tingyuan.
Shen Gu,
they're starting
to suspect your identity.
What are you going to do?
I'll make my identity public.
This is between me, Shen Tingyuan,
and Leng Meng.
It mustn't affect Minghui and Wanxin.
That's my bottom line.
Are you sure?
Once you reveal your identity,
Qingniao's overseas servers could crash.
Your biometric data
will go public instantly.
My identity was going to be exposed
sooner or later.
Better to do it now
and let them come at me.
Don't worry.
Miss Xu wants to climb higher too...
What a twisted narrative.
They're using facts
of marriage and business decisions
and twisting them into a conspiracy.
They used to smear Shen Gu,
now they're targeting you.
They won't let this go.
Xi, what are the trending keywords
about Shen Gu and me right now?
They're saying you're ungrateful,
morally questionable,
that your marriage to Shen Gu is fake,
and that you have an affair
with Qingniao's chairman.
I've prepared a clarification statement.
Don't worry. If the rumors continue,
legal action will follow immediately.
Anjie,
draft the statement now.
Yes.
Anjie.
If we clarify on our own,
it might not have the desired effect.
We're in deep cooperation
with Qingniao.
Why don't we issue a joint statement?
That would not only limit the damage
but also reinforce the public perception
of our strategic alliance.
What do you think?
That makes sense.
I'll make a call.
(Miss Xu)
Boss, it's Miss Xu.
Hello, Miss Xu?
Sorry.
My situation
has caused trouble for your side.
I'd like to invite Qingniao Group
to issue a joint statement with me.
Of course,
I'll personally step forward to clarify.
Wanxin, it's me.
Shen Gu?
Why are you with Qingniao?
Listen to me, Wanxin.
Don't worry.
I'll handle the rumors.
I'm the founder of Qingniao Group
and chief architect, Shen Gu.
Regarding recent rumors
about Minghui Group and Qingniao Group,
please allow me to clarify everything
as Xu Wanxin's husband.
(Interview with Mr. Shen Gu,
Founder of Qingniao Group)
ظآزTonight the rain falls soft and slowظآز
ظآزBlending with letters left unread
drifting through the airظآز
ظآزYou turn and look back at meظآز
ظآزIn those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appearظآز
ظآزIt feels like we have carried so muchظآز
ظآزSo many questions time itself
could not make clearظآز
ظآزThe moment you walked into my lifeظآز
ظآزEvery dream I had became something
I want with you nearظآز
ظآزHow many letters have I written
just for you?ظآز
ظآزIf only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to sayظآز
ظآزFrom this life on
no distance could keep us apartظآز
ظآزThe promise we madeظآز
ظآزWill find its way to be fulfilled
one dayظآز
ظآزBut I want more
than just that fleeting gazeظآز
ظآزStill I have not heard your answerظآز
ظآزCan we still rewrite the ending
we face?ظآز
ظآزWhen regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it allظآز
ظآزEverything that leads me back to youظآز